Maged Khaled Ahmed

Full-Stack Python Developer

in www.linkedin.com/in/maged-khaled-85b150124 www.github.com/MagedKhaled

Profile

Full-Stack Python developer, Started as a freelancer with over 3 years of experience in **Python**, Worked with many technologies during this time, Machine learning, and Data Analysis.

Completed an Internship at ITI Where learned many things about web development, Django, and React in addition to improving my soft skills.

My main goal is to be a professional Python developer so I aim to gain more experience in this field

Internship

ITI, Full-Stack Web Development Using Python Great Opportunity for Both my technical and soft skills

07/2023 - 11/2023 Mansoura, Egypt

Professional Experience

Officer in the Military, *Egypt Military*

2021 - 2023

Served 30 months in the military as an Officer.

Python Developer, Freelance

2018 - 2021

Made More than 5 completed projects and about 30 sub-projects in Machine Learning & Data Analysis.

Education

Bachelor degree in Electrical Engineering, Zagazig University

2014 - 2019

With a Major in Computer Scince

Sharqia, Egypt

Skills

Back-End Skills

Python, Django, Flask

Postgres

API

Front-End Skills

JaveScript, React.js, JQuery HTML,CSS, BootStrap

Odoo

Other Technical Skills

Machin Learning, Data Analysis

Bash Shell Script, Admin1, Linux

Soft Skills

Team Working, Individual Working

Time Management, working under pressure

Communication, Presentation skills

Languages

Arabic

English

intermediate **Mother Language**

Projects

Medadd Website ☑ 06/2023 – 10/2023

Full Website for courses online, Roled as Back-End Python Developer.

Technologies used: Python, Flask, SQLite3, JS, HTML, CSS

Car-Plate detector ☑ 08/2020 – 12/2020

Machine Learning Yolo model used to detect car plate states

Technologies used: Machine Learning, Neural Network, Image Processing

MLDA-Disktop App ☑ 04/2019 – 07/2019

Desktop app made to help employees in big companies to act with millions of data.

Technologies used: Python, Machine Learning, PyQt5, Neural Network, Data

Analysis, Data Visualisation.

Organizations

ZUT

Head of Top20 project provided by ZUT "Zagazig Unlimted Team"

Sharqia, Egypt

IEEE

2015 – 2018

R&D Member in the robotic technical team in IEEE-RAS Zagazig branch

Sharqia, Egypt